{
    "id": "0bbe899f23384e7aaa214f48a6101f9e",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "A year in India initiated him …………………….. the world of spirituality.",
            "description": "Something initiatives somebody into something.",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5211d8ae1e0b4223af26c1b0ccef1e70"
        },
        {
            "question": "The hostess tried to inject some life ……………………………. the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "into",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc0a4f94250b498fb4a302fdee67a07b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Poor management is injurious …………………………. a business.",
            "description": "Injurious takes the preposition to before an object.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4e8ee905653343c693e3a626e746f249"
        },
        {
            "question": "The harsh review was an injury …………………………… the actor’s pride.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "87d3a979069c498382fe59f9a7c430c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mozart had an innate genius ………………………… music.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d6b90fb339fc42b6a525d76a882d6726"
        },
        {
            "question": "She confided her innermost thoughts ………………………….. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cbfe46ff6b734372977c94c87a810b42"
        },
        {
            "question": "The pilot inquired …………………………….. the weather conditions.",
            "description": "To inquire about something is to seek information about it.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "into",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c666c409c0cd46e58324aca06ebe3767"
        },
        {
            "question": "The reporter inquired ……………………………. the rumors of fraud.",
            "description": "To inquire into something is to investigate.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "into",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd96df6daa044ae48be515fe3967234b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The letter made her insane ……………………….. jealousy.",
            "description": "With is used in a number of expressions which say how people show their emotions and sensations.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cda4a6e28d7942d09305abe5bc23d44a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was always insensitive ………………………………. the feelings of others.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1cf8849db350413ba2e2e666c771f0b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He inserted the key …………………………. the lock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bc78af12d4784340822a0916004c6441"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher had unusual insight ………………………….. children’s emotions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "014b4fd9c69b4bfe9536249982b00d3c"
        }
    ]
}